♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 5=
Governor. Miss Jiang is outside,
saying she needs to see you urgently.
Sorry to bother you, Governor.
It's just my father came to talk about
the wedding. He's been waiting a while.
When you'd be available, Governor?
President Jiang is here?
Yes.
Then I'll go meet him.
Take them away.
Young Marshal.
Please.
Mr. Rong.
Miss Jiang.
I just saw they caught someone
from the Rongqing Troupe.
- They're interrogating her now.
- Someone's alive?
Who is it?
I don't know either.
But what if she's tortured
into a false confession?
What if it's detrimental to you?
Just in case, maybe you should slip out
and lie low for a bit?
No, I can't run.
Whoever it is, I must rescue her.
Young Marshal, you should just confess.
Stop pretending.
Who else could steal my army emblem
to frame me besides you?
Young Marshal.
Don't you know the Governor?
You don't really think I'm the only one
who wants to kill you, huh?
You're just a dog he keeps.
Don't flatter yourself.
So it was him all along.
You're so desperate to climb over me.
Trying to get to him,
so you can ask for another bone?
You and I are both orphans he picked up.
I've been with the Governor
just as long as you have.
Why do you get to
keep being the Young Marshal?
marry a rich man's daughter?
Why?
Exactly.
It's always the quiet dogs
that bite the hardest.
He passed out.
Douse him awake!
The Governor still
wants to interrogate him.
If the Young Marshal dies here now,
the Governor will not
spare us if he finds out.
After interrogation and conviction,
we'll have more time to torture him.
You...
Young Marshal.
Why did you help Adjutant Zhao harm me?
Is it a threat with your life,
or a bribe with money?
Speak.
Or I'll strangle you right now.
Who's there?
Down to this state,
and you're still bullying the weak.
Quite the man you are, Young Marshal.
Mr. Rong.
Are you okay?
Let's get you out of here first.
Get out?
Without me,
you'll just die somewhere else.
You're too arrogant.
You're no saint,
and you can't even save yourself.
What makes you think you can help me?
Even if you can
escape the Governor's Mansion, so what?
Where can you hide, and for how long?
Adjutant Zhao used her to set me up.
He's not going to leave any loose ends.
Xu Fan will never let this go either.
Set him up?
Yue Niang.
What's going on?
Mr. Rong, please save my child.
If you truly want to save her,
helping me is the only way.
Then I'll leave this matter to you.
- Governor! Governor!
- Leave this to me.
They tortured the Young Marshal.
Forcing a false confession.
The Young Marshal's unconscious
in jail. He's dying.
(Jiang Xiaoren)
Young Marshal?
(President of Fengcheng
Chamber of Commerce)
He's talking about You'an?
He's dying?
This...
You fool!
Who dared torture You'an
before the matter was investigated?
It was Adjutant Zhao.
He said it was under your orders.
Please investigate clearly.
March 16th, I was with the Young Marshal
inspecting the northern defenses.
I swear he never went to Rongqing Troupe
and met Head Rong.
The 16th of last month?
Wasn't that His Lordship's birthday?
Dad.
Do you remember that day?
We all went to His Lordship's birthday.
We saw Rong Xiaonan and Head Rong there.
They were invited to perform.
So how could he have been
at the Rongqing Troupe?
Right, right.
I remember now.
Dad.
There must be a misunderstanding.
He's hurt so close to the wedding.
Will it delay my auspicious wedding day?
Governor, this...
Go.
Have Adjutant Zhao bring the him out
and find a doctor to take a good look.
Yes.
Jiang.
Don't worry.
I will thoroughly
investigate this matter.
Move.
Only dead people can keep secrets.
You and your child should just die.
Quick, pick up the gun!
Speak! Where is the child?
Governor.
No sign of the real Buddha Head
or the other artifacts.
I fear we won't be able to answer
to Xiaosheng Society or the Japanese.
Rong Xiaonan, shoot!
(Rong Xiaonan!)
(It was Xu Fan who killed master.)
Shoot!
Xu You'an.
- Mr. Rong, go quickly!
- Just die!
Mr. Rong, go quickly! Go save my child!
It was you.
It was you!
I will avenge my master
and everyone in the Rongqing Troupe!
You're asking to die!
♪Candle by the west window♪
♪Burned out this life♪
♪Ending in nothingness♪
♪I ask why♪
♪I yearn for the one who's gone
through heat and cold♪
♪A handful of earth♪
♪The world's last gamble♪
♪Sighing at the late hour♪
♪No one comes to meet me♪
♪Candle by the west window♪
♪Burned out this life♪
♪Ending in nothingness♪
♪I ask why♪
♪I yearn for the one who's gone
through heat and cold♪
♪A handful of earth♪
♪The world's last gamble♪
♪Sighing at the late hour♪
♪No one comes to meet me♪
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪